[
    {
        "question": "さ来年",
        "answer": "さらいねん"
    },
    {
        "question": "大きい",
        "answer": "おおきい"
    },
    {
        "question": "英語",
        "answer": "えいご"
    },
    {
        "question": "終る",
        "answer": "おわる"
    },
    {
        "question": "秋",
        "answer": "あき"
    },
    {
        "question": "朝",
        "answer": "あさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "大好き",
        "answer": "だいすき"
    },
    {
        "question": "喫茶店",
        "answer": "きっさてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "話す",
        "answer": "はなす"
    },
    {
        "question": "覚える",
        "answer": "おぼえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "小さな",
        "answer": "ちいさな"
    },
    {
        "question": "四日",
        "answer": "よっか"
    },
    {
        "question": "時々",
        "answer": "ときどき"
    },
    {
        "question": "冬",
        "answer": "ふゆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "目",
        "answer": "め"
    },
    {
        "question": "灰皿",
        "answer": "はいざら"
    },
    {
        "question": "散歩",
        "answer": "さんぽする"
    },
    {
        "question": "有名",
        "answer": "ゆうめい"
    },
    {
        "question": "姉",
        "answer": "あね"
    },
    {
        "question": "吹く",
        "answer": "ふく"
    },
    {
        "question": "上",
        "answer": "うえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "出口",
        "answer": "でぐち"
    },
    {
        "question": "次",
        "answer": "つぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "百",
        "answer": "ひゃく"
    },
    {
        "question": "背広",
        "answer": "せびろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "本棚",
        "answer": "ほんだな"
    },
    {
        "question": "十",
        "answer": "じゅう  とお"
    },
    {
        "question": "登る",
        "answer": "のぼる"
    },
    {
        "question": "体",
        "answer": "からだ"
    },
    {
        "question": "水曜日",
        "answer": "すいようび"
    },
    {
        "question": "封筒",
        "answer": "ふうとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "茶色",
        "answer": "ちゃいろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "起きる",
        "answer": "おきる"
    },
    {
        "question": "賑やか",
        "answer": "にぎやか"
    },
    {
        "question": "習う",
        "answer": "ならう"
    },
    {
        "question": "働く",
        "answer": "はたらく"
    },
    {
        "question": "学校",
        "answer": "がっこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "弟",
        "answer": "おとうと"
    },
    {
        "question": "牛乳",
        "answer": "ぎゅうにゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "お金",
        "answer": "おかね"
    },
    {
        "question": "電話",
        "answer": "でんわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "風",
        "answer": "かぜ"
    },
    {
        "question": "毎年",
        "answer": [
            "まいねん",
            "まいとし"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "隣",
        "answer": "となり"
    },
    {
        "question": "二つ",
        "answer": "ふたつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "読む",
        "answer": "よむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "土曜日",
        "answer": "どようび"
    },
    {
        "question": "歌",
        "answer": "うた"
    },
    {
        "question": "意味",
        "answer": "いみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "生まれる",
        "answer": "うまれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "吸う",
        "answer": "すう"
    },
    {
        "question": "所",
        "answer": "ところ"
    },
    {
        "question": "脱ぐ",
        "answer": "ぬぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "全部",
        "answer": "ぜんぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "牛肉",
        "answer": "ぎゅうにく"
    },
    {
        "question": "着く",
        "answer": "つく"
    },
    {
        "question": "午前",
        "answer": "ごぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "薬",
        "answer": "くすり"
    },
    {
        "question": "八つ",
        "answer": "やっつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "危ない",
        "answer": "あぶない"
    },
    {
        "question": "降る",
        "answer": "ふる"
    },
    {
        "question": "言う",
        "answer": "いう"
    },
    {
        "question": "休む",
        "answer": "やすむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "花",
        "answer": "はな"
    },
    {
        "question": "二十日",
        "answer": "はつか"
    },
    {
        "question": "三",
        "answer": "さん"
    },
    {
        "question": "嫌い",
        "answer": "きらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "飲み物",
        "answer": "のみもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "南",
        "answer": "みなみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "困る",
        "answer": "こまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "二日",
        "answer": "ふつか"
    },
    {
        "question": "警官",
        "answer": "けいかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "二人",
        "answer": "ふたり"
    },
    {
        "question": "午後",
        "answer": "ごご"
    },
    {
        "question": "今日",
        "answer": "きょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "一日",
        "answer": ["いちにち", "ついたち"]
    },
    {
        "question": "入れる",
        "answer": "いれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "今週",
        "answer": "こんしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "空",
        "answer": "そら"
    },
    {
        "question": "黄色い",
        "answer": "きいろい"
    },
    {
        "question": "地下鉄",
        "answer": "ちかてつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "留学生",
        "answer": "りゅうがくせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "持つ",
        "answer": "もつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "池",
        "answer": "いけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "猫",
        "answer": "ねこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "今月",
        "answer": "こんげつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "左",
        "answer": "ひだり"
    },
    {
        "question": "聞く",
        "answer": "きく"
    },
    {
        "question": "休み",
        "answer": "やすみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "要る",
        "answer": "いる"
    },
    {
        "question": "新聞",
        "answer": "しんぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "立つ",
        "answer": "たつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "何",
        "answer": [
            "なん",
            "なに"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "足",
        "answer": "あし"
    },
    {
        "question": "静か",
        "answer": "しずか"
    },
    {
        "question": "お父さん",
        "answer": "おとうさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "元気",
        "answer": "げんき"
    },
    {
        "question": "名前",
        "answer": "なまえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "降りる",
        "answer": "おりる"
    },
    {
        "question": "向こう",
        "answer": "むこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "庭",
        "answer": "にわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "映画館",
        "answer": "えいがかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "一",
        "answer": "いち"
    },
    {
        "question": "頭",
        "answer": "あたま"
    },
    {
        "question": "交番",
        "answer": "こうばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "廊下",
        "answer": "ろうか"
    },
    {
        "question": "郵便局",
        "answer": "ゆうびんきょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "一緒",
        "answer": "いっしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "村",
        "answer": "むら"
    },
    {
        "question": "磨く",
        "answer": "みがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "痛い",
        "answer": "いたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "零",
        "answer": "れい"
    },
    {
        "question": "電気",
        "answer": "でんき"
    },
    {
        "question": "始まる",
        "answer": "はじまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "座る",
        "answer": "すわる"
    },
    {
        "question": "夏休み",
        "answer": "なつやすみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "毎晩",
        "answer": "まいばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "洋服",
        "answer": "ようふく"
    },
    {
        "question": "外",
        "answer": "そと"
    },
    {
        "question": "辺",
        "answer": "へん"
    },
    {
        "question": "伯母さん/叔母さん",
        "answer": "おばさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "教室",
        "answer": "きょうしつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "年",
        "answer": "とし"
    },
    {
        "question": "火曜日",
        "answer": "かようび"
    },
    {
        "question": "飴",
        "answer": "あめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "昼",
        "answer": "ひる"
    },
    {
        "question": "時計",
        "answer": "とけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "映画",
        "answer": "えいが"
    },
    {
        "question": "並べる",
        "answer": "ならべる"
    },
    {
        "question": "大丈夫",
        "answer": "だいじょうぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "来週",
        "answer": "らいしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "下手",
        "answer": "へた"
    },
    {
        "question": "病気",
        "answer": "びょうき"
    },
    {
        "question": "絵",
        "answer": "え"
    },
    {
        "question": "閉まる",
        "answer": "しまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "戸",
        "answer": "と"
    },
    {
        "question": "靴",
        "answer": "くつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "方",
        "answer": "かた"
    },
    {
        "question": "来る",
        "answer": "くる"
    },
    {
        "question": "忙しい",
        "answer": "いそがしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "売る",
        "answer": "うる"
    },
    {
        "question": "町",
        "answer": "まち"
    },
    {
        "question": "消す",
        "answer": "けす"
    },
    {
        "question": "毎日",
        "answer": "まいにち"
    },
    {
        "question": "難しい",
        "answer": "むずかしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "帰る",
        "answer": "かえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "中",
        "answer": "なか"
    },
    {
        "question": "今",
        "answer": "いま"
    },
    {
        "question": "短い",
        "answer": "みじかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "食堂",
        "answer": "しょくどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "古い",
        "answer": "ふるい"
    },
    {
        "question": "軽い",
        "answer": "かるい"
    },
    {
        "question": "道",
        "answer": "みち"
    },
    {
        "question": "万年筆",
        "answer": "まんねんひつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "本",
        "answer": "ほん"
    },
    {
        "question": "買う",
        "answer": "かう"
    },
    {
        "question": "授業",
        "answer": "じゅぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "渡る",
        "answer": "わたる"
    },
    {
        "question": "死ぬ",
        "answer": "しぬ"
    },
    {
        "question": "大人",
        "answer": "おとな"
    },
    {
        "question": "赤",
        "answer": "あか"
    },
    {
        "question": "妹",
        "answer": "いもうと"
    },
    {
        "question": "机",
        "answer": "つくえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "背",
        "answer": "せ"
    },
    {
        "question": "東",
        "answer": "ひがし"
    },
    {
        "question": "返す",
        "answer": "かえす"
    },
    {
        "question": "橋",
        "answer": "はし"
    },
    {
        "question": "一昨年",
        "answer": "おととし"
    },
    {
        "question": "低い",
        "answer": "ひくい"
    },
    {
        "question": "差す",
        "answer": "さす"
    },
    {
        "question": "お姉さん",
        "answer": "おねえさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "雪",
        "answer": "ゆき"
    },
    {
        "question": "新しい",
        "answer": "あたらしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "電車",
        "answer": "でんしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "写真",
        "answer": "しゃしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "私",
        "answer": "わたくし"
    },
    {
        "question": "飛行機",
        "answer": "ひこうき"
    },
    {
        "question": "晩",
        "answer": "ばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "飛ぶ",
        "answer": "とぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "熱い",
        "answer": "あつい"
    },
    {
        "question": "前",
        "answer": "まえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "去年",
        "answer": "きょねん"
    },
    {
        "question": "洗濯",
        "answer": "せんたく"
    },
    {
        "question": "掃除",
        "answer": "そうじする"
    },
    {
        "question": "安い",
        "answer": "やすい"
    },
    {
        "question": "緑",
        "answer": "みどり"
    },
    {
        "question": "下",
        "answer": "した"
    },
    {
        "question": "先週",
        "answer": "せんしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "お弁当",
        "answer": "おべんとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "手紙",
        "answer": "てがみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "字引",
        "answer": "じびき"
    },
    {
        "question": "大切",
        "answer": "たいせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "二",
        "answer": "に"
    },
    {
        "question": "嫌",
        "answer": "いや"
    },
    {
        "question": "九",
        "answer": [
            "きゅう",
            "く"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "弾く",
        "answer": "ひく"
    },
    {
        "question": "丸い/円い",
        "answer": "まるい"
    },
    {
        "question": "友達",
        "answer": "ともだち"
    },
    {
        "question": "黒",
        "answer": "くろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "口",
        "answer": "くち"
    },
    {
        "question": "誕生日",
        "answer": "たんじょうび"
    },
    {
        "question": "毎朝",
        "answer": "まいあさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "教える",
        "answer": "おしえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "日曜日",
        "answer": "にちようび"
    },
    {
        "question": "お皿",
        "answer": "おさら"
    },
    {
        "question": "撮る",
        "answer": "とる"
    },
    {
        "question": "歌う",
        "answer": "うたう"
    },
    {
        "question": "医者",
        "answer": "いしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "半分",
        "answer": "はんぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "外国",
        "answer": "がいこく"
    },
    {
        "question": "葉書",
        "answer": "はがき"
    },
    {
        "question": "六",
        "answer": "ろく"
    },
    {
        "question": "言葉",
        "answer": "ことば"
    },
    {
        "question": "木曜日",
        "answer": "もくようび"
    },
    {
        "question": "卵",
        "answer": "たまご"
    },
    {
        "question": "厚い",
        "answer": "あつい"
    },
    {
        "question": "図書館",
        "answer": "としょかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "汚い",
        "answer": "きたない"
    },
    {
        "question": "今朝",
        "answer": "けさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "寝る",
        "answer": "ねる"
    },
    {
        "question": "毎週",
        "answer": "まいしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "曇り",
        "answer": "くもり"
    },
    {
        "question": "木",
        "answer": "き"
    },
    {
        "question": "多い",
        "answer": "おおい"
    },
    {
        "question": "三日",
        "answer": "みっか"
    },
    {
        "question": "甘い",
        "answer": "あまい"
    },
    {
        "question": "書く",
        "answer": "かく"
    },
    {
        "question": "消える",
        "answer": "きえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "上げる",
        "answer": "あげる"
    },
    {
        "question": "遅い",
        "answer": "おそい"
    },
    {
        "question": "手",
        "answer": "て"
    },
    {
        "question": "台所",
        "answer": "だいどころ"
    },
    {
        "question": "夜",
        "answer": "よる"
    },
    {
        "question": "先",
        "answer": "さき"
    },
    {
        "question": "青い",
        "answer": "あおい"
    },
    {
        "question": "白",
        "answer": "しろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "仕事",
        "answer": "しごと"
    },
    {
        "question": "曇る",
        "answer": "くもる"
    },
    {
        "question": "丈夫",
        "answer": "じょうぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "色",
        "answer": "いろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "締める",
        "answer": "しめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "月曜日",
        "answer": "げつようび"
    },
    {
        "question": "出かける",
        "answer": "でかける"
    },
    {
        "question": "豚肉",
        "answer": "ぶたにく"
    },
    {
        "question": "七つ",
        "answer": "ななつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "五つ",
        "answer": "いつつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "九日",
        "answer": "ここのか"
    },
    {
        "question": "御飯",
        "answer": "ごはん"
    },
    {
        "question": "開く",
        "answer": "あく"
    },
    {
        "question": "咲く",
        "answer": "さく"
    },
    {
        "question": "大勢",
        "answer": "おおぜい"
    },
    {
        "question": "遊ぶ",
        "answer": "あそぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "上着",
        "answer": "うわぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "自動車",
        "answer": "じどうしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "三つ",
        "answer": "みっつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "兄弟",
        "answer": "きょうだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "止まる",
        "answer": "とまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "お兄さん",
        "answer": "おにいさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "結構",
        "answer": "けっこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "結婚",
        "answer": "けっこん"
    },
    {
        "question": "明い",
        "answer": "あかるい"
    },
    {
        "question": "女の子",
        "answer": "おんなのこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "出る",
        "answer": "でる"
    },
    {
        "question": "窓",
        "answer": "まど"
    },
    {
        "question": "会社",
        "answer": "かいしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "悪い",
        "answer": "わるい"
    },
    {
        "question": "国",
        "answer": "くに"
    },
    {
        "question": "初めて",
        "answer": "はじめて"
    },
    {
        "question": "靴下",
        "answer": "くつした"
    },
    {
        "question": "違う",
        "answer": "ちがう"
    },
    {
        "question": "寒い",
        "answer": "さむい"
    },
    {
        "question": "雨",
        "answer": "あめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "少し",
        "answer": "すこし"
    },
    {
        "question": "明日",
        "answer": "あした"
    },
    {
        "question": "晩御飯",
        "answer": "ばんごはん"
    },
    {
        "question": "便利",
        "answer": "べんり"
    },
    {
        "question": "着る",
        "answer": "きる"
    },
    {
        "question": "もう一度",
        "answer": "もういちど"
    },
    {
        "question": "速い",
        "answer": "はやい"
    },
    {
        "question": "宿題",
        "answer": "しゅくだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "辞書",
        "answer": "じしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "開ける",
        "answer": "あける"
    },
    {
        "question": "入口",
        "answer": "いりぐち"
    },
    {
        "question": "七",
        "answer": [
            "しち",
            "なな"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "後ろ",
        "answer": "うしろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "好き",
        "answer": "すき"
    },
    {
        "question": "住む",
        "answer": "すむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "夕飯",
        "answer": "ゆうはん"
    },
    {
        "question": "暖かい",
        "answer": "あたたかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "六つ",
        "answer": "むっつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "家族",
        "answer": "かぞく"
    },
    {
        "question": "重い",
        "answer": "おもい"
    },
    {
        "question": "万",
        "answer": "まん"
    },
    {
        "question": "暇",
        "answer": "ひま"
    },
    {
        "question": "会う",
        "answer": "あう"
    },
    {
        "question": "病院",
        "answer": "びょういん"
    },
    {
        "question": "薄い",
        "answer": "うすい"
    },
    {
        "question": "歯",
        "answer": "は"
    },
    {
        "question": "山",
        "answer": "やま"
    },
    {
        "question": "質問",
        "answer": "しつもん"
    },
    {
        "question": "忘れる",
        "answer": "わすれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "水",
        "answer": "みず"
    },
    {
        "question": "黒い",
        "answer": "くろい"
    },
    {
        "question": "八",
        "answer": "はち"
    },
    {
        "question": "晴れる",
        "answer": "はれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "右",
        "answer": "みぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "声",
        "answer": "こえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "取る",
        "answer": "とる"
    },
    {
        "question": "海",
        "answer": "うみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "白い",
        "answer": "しろい"
    },
    {
        "question": "六日",
        "answer": "むいか"
    },
    {
        "question": "魚",
        "answer": "さかな"
    },
    {
        "question": "犬",
        "answer": "いぬ"
    },
    {
        "question": "後",
        "answer": "あと"
    },
    {
        "question": "八日",
        "answer": "ようか"
    },
    {
        "question": "お菓子",
        "answer": "おかし"
    },
    {
        "question": "見せる",
        "answer": "みせる"
    },
    {
        "question": "冷たい",
        "answer": "つめたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "貼る",
        "answer": "はる"
    },
    {
        "question": "暗い",
        "answer": "くらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "今晩",
        "answer": "こんばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "昨夜",
        "answer": "ゆうべ"
    },
    {
        "question": "曲る",
        "answer": "まがる"
    },
    {
        "question": "七日",
        "answer": "なのか"
    },
    {
        "question": "高い",
        "answer": "たかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "荷物",
        "answer": "にもつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "川/河",
        "answer": "かわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "黄色",
        "answer": "きいろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "引く",
        "answer": "ひく"
    },
    {
        "question": "易しい",
        "answer": "やさしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "太い",
        "answer": "ふとい"
    },
    {
        "question": "朝御飯",
        "answer": "あさごはん"
    },
    {
        "question": "生徒",
        "answer": "せいと"
    },
    {
        "question": "階段",
        "answer": "かいだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "問題",
        "answer": "もんだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "玄関",
        "answer": "げんかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "金曜日",
        "answer": "きんようび"
    },
    {
        "question": "五",
        "answer": "ご"
    },
    {
        "question": "公園",
        "answer": "こうえん"
    },
    {
        "question": "楽しい",
        "answer": "たのしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "一昨日",
        "answer": "おととい"
    },
    {
        "question": "肉",
        "answer": "にく"
    },
    {
        "question": "西",
        "answer": "にし"
    },
    {
        "question": "同じ",
        "answer": "おなじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "若い",
        "answer": "わかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "果物",
        "answer": "くだもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "入る",
        "answer": "はいる"
    },
    {
        "question": "頼む",
        "answer": "たのむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "知る",
        "answer": "しる"
    },
    {
        "question": "飲む",
        "answer": "のむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "出す",
        "answer": "だす"
    },
    {
        "question": "両親",
        "answer": "りょうしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "二十歳",
        "answer": "はたち"
    },
    {
        "question": "小さい",
        "answer": "ちいさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "疲れる",
        "answer": "つかれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "鳥",
        "answer": "とり"
    },
    {
        "question": "借りる",
        "answer": "かりる"
    },
    {
        "question": "雑誌",
        "answer": "ざっし"
    },
    {
        "question": "家",
        "answer": "いえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "店",
        "answer": "みせ"
    },
    {
        "question": "番号",
        "answer": "ばんごう"
    },
    {
        "question": "青",
        "answer": "あお"
    },
    {
        "question": "紙",
        "answer": "かみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "練習",
        "answer": "れんしゅうする"
    },
    {
        "question": "花瓶",
        "answer": "かびん"
    },
    {
        "question": "一つ",
        "answer": "ひとつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "食べる",
        "answer": "たべる"
    },
    {
        "question": "誰",
        "answer": "だれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "長い",
        "answer": "ながい"
    },
    {
        "question": "遠い",
        "answer": "とおい"
    },
    {
        "question": "八百屋",
        "answer": "やおや"
    },
    {
        "question": "少ない",
        "answer": "すくない"
    },
    {
        "question": "砂糖",
        "answer": "さとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "お母さん",
        "answer": "おかあさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "食べ物",
        "answer": "たべもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "置く",
        "answer": "おく"
    },
    {
        "question": "昨日",
        "answer": "きのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "帽子",
        "answer": "ぼうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "毎月",
        "answer": [
            "まいげつ",
            "まいつき"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "切符",
        "answer": "きっぷ"
    },
    {
        "question": "作る",
        "answer": "つくる"
    },
    {
        "question": "居る",
        "answer": "いる"
    },
    {
        "question": "鼻",
        "answer": "はな"
    },
    {
        "question": "箱",
        "answer": "はこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "動物",
        "answer": "どうぶつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "交差点",
        "answer": "こうさてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "話",
        "answer": "はなし"
    },
    {
        "question": "財布",
        "answer": "さいふ"
    },
    {
        "question": "使う",
        "answer": "つかう"
    },
    {
        "question": "昼御飯",
        "answer": "ひるごはん"
    },
    {
        "question": "塩",
        "answer": "しお"
    },
    {
        "question": "千",
        "answer": "せん"
    },
    {
        "question": "時間",
        "answer": "じかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "文章",
        "answer": "ぶんしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "勉強",
        "answer": "べんきょうする"
    },
    {
        "question": "夏",
        "answer": "なつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "答える",
        "answer": "こたえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "閉める",
        "answer": "しめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "大使館",
        "answer": "たいしかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "お手洗い",
        "answer": "おてあらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "弱い",
        "answer": "よわい"
    },
    {
        "question": "涼しい",
        "answer": "すずしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "今年",
        "answer": "ことし"
    },
    {
        "question": "辛い",
        "answer": "からい"
    },
    {
        "question": "近く",
        "answer": "ちかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "四つ",
        "answer": "よっつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "物",
        "answer": "もの"
    },
    {
        "question": "押す",
        "answer": "おす"
    },
    {
        "question": "先生",
        "answer": "せんせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "学生",
        "answer": "がくせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "走る",
        "answer": "はしる"
    },
    {
        "question": "早い",
        "answer": "はやい"
    },
    {
        "question": "外国人",
        "answer": "がいこくじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "女",
        "answer": "おんな"
    },
    {
        "question": "横",
        "answer": "よこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "泳ぐ",
        "answer": "およぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "鳴く",
        "answer": "なく"
    },
    {
        "question": "無くす",
        "answer": "なくす"
    },
    {
        "question": "初め/始め",
        "answer": "はじめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "切手",
        "answer": "きって"
    },
    {
        "question": "作文",
        "answer": "さくぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "五日",
        "answer": "いつか"
    },
    {
        "question": "傘",
        "answer": "かさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "赤い",
        "answer": "あかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "お風呂",
        "answer": "おふろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "兄",
        "answer": "あに"
    },
    {
        "question": "春",
        "answer": "はる"
    },
    {
        "question": "旅行",
        "answer": "りょこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "来月",
        "answer": "らいげつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "十日",
        "answer": "とおか"
    },
    {
        "question": "見る  観る",
        "answer": "みる"
    },
    {
        "question": "渡す",
        "answer": "わたす"
    },
    {
        "question": "奥さん",
        "answer": "おくさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "広い",
        "answer": "ひろい"
    },
    {
        "question": "一月",
        "answer": ["ひとつき", "いちがつ"]
    },
    {
        "question": "半",
        "answer": "はん"
    },
    {
        "question": "皆さん",
        "answer": "みなさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "男",
        "answer": "おとこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "服",
        "answer": "ふく"
    },
    {
        "question": "風邪",
        "answer": "かぜ"
    },
    {
        "question": "暑い",
        "answer": "あつい"
    },
    {
        "question": "行く",
        "answer": "いく"
    },
    {
        "question": "切る",
        "answer": "きる"
    },
    {
        "question": "待つ",
        "answer": "まつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "人",
        "answer": "ひと"
    },
    {
        "question": "角",
        "answer": "かど"
    },
    {
        "question": "車",
        "answer": "くるま"
    },
    {
        "question": "細い",
        "answer": "ほそい"
    },
    {
        "question": "鉛筆",
        "answer": "えんぴつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "銀行",
        "answer": "ぎんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "お酒",
        "answer": "おさけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "狭い",
        "answer": "せまい"
    },
    {
        "question": "強い",
        "answer": "つよい"
    },
    {
        "question": "お茶",
        "answer": "おちゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "野菜",
        "answer": "やさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "地図",
        "answer": "ちず"
    },
    {
        "question": "先月",
        "answer": "せんげつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "冷蔵庫",
        "answer": "れいぞうこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "部屋",
        "answer": "へや"
    },
    {
        "question": "来年",
        "answer": "らいねん"
    },
    {
        "question": "眼鏡",
        "answer": "めがね"
    },
    {
        "question": "洗う",
        "answer": "あらう"
    },
    {
        "question": "子供",
        "answer": "こども"
    },
    {
        "question": "自転車",
        "answer": "じてんしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "伯父/叔父",
        "answer": "おじいさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "自分",
        "answer": "じぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "勤める",
        "answer": "つとめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "家庭",
        "answer": "かてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "北",
        "answer": "きた"
    },
    {
        "question": "並ぶ",
        "answer": "ならぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "晴れ",
        "answer": "はれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "呼ぶ",
        "answer": "よぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "歩く",
        "answer": "あるく"
    },
    {
        "question": "貸す",
        "answer": "かす"
    },
    {
        "question": "料理",
        "answer": "りょうり"
    },
    {
        "question": "近い",
        "answer": "ちかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "欲しい",
        "answer": "ほしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "大きな",
        "answer": "おおきな"
    },
    {
        "question": "耳",
        "answer": "みみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "温い",
        "answer": "ぬるい"
    },
    {
        "question": "一人",
        "answer": "ひとり"
    },
    {
        "question": "四",
        "answer": [
            "し",
            "よん"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "九つ",
        "answer": "ここのつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "漢字",
        "answer": "かんじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "分かる",
        "answer": "わかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "大学",
        "answer": "だいがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "上手",
        "answer": "じょうず"
    },
    {
        "question": "男の子",
        "answer": "おとこのこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "天気",
        "answer": "てんき"
    },
    {
        "question": "紅茶",
        "answer": "こうちゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "夕方",
        "answer": "ゆうがた"
    },
    {
        "question": "駅",
        "answer": "えき"
    },
    {
        "question": "門",
        "answer": "もん"
    },
    {
        "question": "煩い",
        "answer": "うるさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "建物",
        "answer": "たてもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "買い物",
        "answer": "かいもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "乗る",
        "answer": "のる"
    },
    {
        "question": "音楽",
        "answer": "おんがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "とり肉",
        "answer": "とりにく"
    }
]